Hey, I'm Chuck.
Here's a couple of things
안녕하세요, 척이예요
몇 가지 아셔야 할 얘기가 있어요
잊어버리셔도 되고요
that you might need to know
or maybe you just forgot.
So, do you have a girlfriend?
여자 친구 있어요?
I did a while back at Stanford.
예전에 스탠포드 다닐 땐 있었어요
Oh.
- Yeah her name was Jill.
질이라는 애였는데
We met freshmen year.
1학년 때 만났죠
We had so much in common then.
우리 진짜 잘 통했었는데..
Bryce Larkin.
브라이스 라킨이라고
Dude pretended to be his buddy
척 친구인 척 하면서
얘 여자친구랑 자고
sexed up his girl and got him
kicked out of Stanford.
척을 스탠포드에서
쫓겨나게 만든 놈이예요
스탠포드 일은 5년 전 일이야
Stanford was five years ago.
You need to move on.
이제 그만 잊어버려
Fine, I'll get over Jill tomorrow.
알았어. 나중에 다 잊을게
2003년 스탠포드 대학교
♪ Iggy Pop - Pumpin' for Jill ♪
자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
영문자막 : www.shooter.cn
싱크편집 / 한글번역
김호정(hojeong_@nate.com)
Hey, Chuck!
안녕 척
That's the dude that got
쟤가 컨닝때문에 학교 짤린 애야
kicked out for cheating.
Yeah, I didn't cheat,
actually, it's...
나 컨닝 안 했거든
Oh! Hey, I'm just--
안녕. 나 이것 좀 빌릴게
If you guys don't mind,
I'm just gonna borrow these.
Continue with your game.
게임 하던거 마저 해
Gonna have to turn
this off, too.
그리고 이것도 좀 끌게
Jill!
질
Come on.
Jill! Hey!
질
나야 척이야
IT'S CHUCK.
제발 나한테 직접 설명할 기회를 줘
Please, I-I want a chance
to explain my side face-to-face.
질이 너랑 얘길 하고 싶었으면
If Jill wanted
to speak to you
네가 28번 전화했을 때
이미 받았겠지
she would have returned
one of your 28 phone calls.
안녕 쉐리
Hi, Shari.
질 거기 있어?
Is she up there?
질
Jill...
나..
I, uh,
지금 잠깐 쉬는시간에 나온거야
I was on break at-at work.
지금 바이모어에서 일하고 있거든
I'm actually working
at a Buy More.
많고 많은 곳 중에 하필 거기야
Of all places, yeah.
버뱅크에서 여기까지
557킬로나 운전해서 온거야
And I drove, you know,
346 miles straight
from Burbank
널 만나서
여전히 사랑한다고 얘기하고 싶어서
to see you and to tell you
that I still love you.
패배자!
Loser!
척!
Chuck!
안녕 질!
Hey, hey, Jill!
저기 나 공개적으로
망신 충분히 당한 것 같은데
Hey, um, I think
I've thoroughly publicly
embarrassed myself enough,
이제 올라가서 커피나 마시면서
얘기 좀 해도 될까?
so you think maybe we could go
talk over some coffee
or something like that?
늦었어 척. 다 끝났어
It's too late, Chuck. It's over.
다 끝났단 얘긴 지금
이 대화는 끝났다는 얘기지?
When you say "it's over,"
you mean, like, this
conversation's over, right?
그니까 스타벅스에서 마저 얘기하자는거지?
To be continued
at the Starbucks?
얘 이제 브라이스 라킨이랑 사겨, 척
She's dating Bryce Larkin
now, Chuck.
브라이스... / 받아들여
Bryce...
Deal with it.
I told you he was a loser.
사실이야?
Is that true?
미안해, 척
I'm sorry, Chuck.
생각을 방해하고 싶진 않지만
Oh, I hate to disturb
youreverie there, ChucK
쉐라톤 국제회의 센터에서
기술 지원 요청이 왔으니
I'm going to need you
to get down to the
Sheraton Conference Center
거기 좀 다녀오세요
for a tech-support call.
지금 당장
Pronto.
네 갈게요, 에밋
Sure thing, Emmet.
그 상자, 보스턴 크림인가요?
Got any Boston cream in there?
네, 여러 개 있어요
Oh, yeah, several.
Ah...
에밋, 이럴 것까진 없는데
Why, Emmet, you shouldn't have.
정말 맛있게 생겼죠?
Oh, they just look delicious.
이런
Oh, my God.
목에 걸리셨어요?
You breathing?
진정, 진정하세요
Try to relax.
이런 맙소사
Oh, my God!
도와줘요! 위급상황이예요!
Help! This man's dying!
아니예요 에밋 잘못하고
있잖아요. 그게 아니고
No, no, Emmet, Emmet, you're doing it wrong--
you're supposed
입을 열어서 음식을 꺼내야죠
to hold his mouth open,
reach down and grab it.
그 방법도 되나보네요
Guess that way
works, too.
도넛 또 없어요?
Are there any more donuts?
생명과학 회의군요
Huh, BioScience conference.
일이 꽤나 힘드시겠어요
I bet these things
get pretty wild, huh?
자 이제 회의실에는 방화벽과
모든 서버와 연결된
All right, so the networks
should now be all set up
with ten-based T Ethernet
connecting all the servers
연결된 10 베이스-T 이더넷으로
네트워크 설정해뒀고요
for the conference
with a firewall in place.
괜찮으세요?
Is there a problem?
저 쪽에 냉정하고 갈색 눈에 똑똑해보이고
Can you tell me
if the attractive brown-eyed,
slightly egg-headed brunette
갈색 머리에 매력적인 여자가
아직도 여기 있나요?
with an extremely cold heart
is still here?
네 있어요
She's here.
왜요? 누군데요?
Why? Who is she?
질 로버츠라고 예전 여자친군데
절 뻥 차버렸어요
Jill Roberts, my ex-girlfriend.
She broke my heart.
시선을 다른데로 돌려야겠는데
I need, I need a diversion.
화재 경보기를 눌러 달라고하면
지나친 부탁일까요?
Would it be
a terrible imposition
for you to pull
the fire alarm?
안녕하세요
질 로버츠 박사라고 하는데요
Hi, I'm Dr. Jill Roberts.
Is there someone
제 강연에 기술적으로 도움이 필요한데
도와주실 분이 있나요?
that can help me with the tech requirements
for my lecture?
이 책상 밑에요
Under the desk.
뭐?
What?
안녕하세요
Hi.
척?
Chuck?
Ah!
이음새 문제였네요
It was the flange just there.
척 바토스키
Chuck Bartowski.
네
네. 전데요
Present.
Yes, that's me.
나야 질
It's me, Jill.
질이구나, 세상에
너구나!
Jill, oh, my gosh! Of course!
Yes.
안녕 / 안녕
- Hi.
그래 너구나!
Hey, you!
어떻게 지내?
- How are you?!
- Good.
이렇게 만나니까..
정말 반갑다
So good to...
see you.
그래 나도 반가워
이게 얼마만이지?
You, too
How long has it been?
5년하고도 4달...정도?
Five years, four months-ish,
그래 아마 그 정도쯤 될거야
give or take,
kind of in that neighborhood.
어떻게 지냈니?
Uh, what have you been up to?
스탠포드 졸업 후에
생물 의·공학 박사 학위를 받았어
Uh, well, after Stanford,
I got my PhD in biomedical
engineering.
정말?
Did you?
응 오늘 회의에서 전염병에 대한
발표를 하기로 해서 온거야
Yeah. I'm giving a presentation
at the conference
on infectious diseases.
잘됐다
Lovely.
- 넌 어떻게 지냈어?
- 나는...
And you?
And me.
아직 컴퓨터 게임에 빠져있어
Uh-uh still in the computer
game, you know?
작, 작은 회사 차려서
일하고 있어
Yeah, I-I-I work?wn
my own little,
little-little company.
지점이 16갠가, 17갠가
기억이 안 나네
16, 17-- I can't remember
which-- stores.
그래도 가끔은 내가 직접
다니면서 일하는 것도 좋더라고
But every once
in a while
I like to do the installs
myself, you know,
유니폼도 입고
손에 이것 저것 묻혀가면서 말이지
don the uni, kind of
get my hands mussy.
정말 잘됐다, 척
I'm really happy
for you, Chuck.
우리가 마지막으로 만났을 때
The-the last time
I saw you were--
바이모어에서 일하고 있었잖아
you were working
at a Buy More.
Ah!
정말 굉장한 경험이었지
That was a wonderful
growing experience.
지금의 내가 되는데 도움이 됐어
Really, really
character building.
무엇과도 바꾸고 싶지 않은 일이야
And I wouldn't-- wouldn't
change it for the world.
Well...
난 바꾸고 싶은 일이 있어
there's definitely some
things I would change.
우리 일 말이야
Especially about us.
여깄었네
There you are.
우리 늦었어
- We're running late.
-Oh.
기 씨. 여긴 제 친구
척 바토스키예요
Guy, this is
my old friend
Chuck Bartowski--
Chuck, this is my boss
척, 이 분은 내 보스
기 르플뢰르 씨
Guy LeFleur.
안녕하세요 반갑습니다
Hi. Nice to meet you.
제가 세균 연구를
하는 사람이라..
I work with germs,
so, you know.
EMTREMELY HAZADOUS
친구 분은 컴퓨터 때문에
바쁘신 것 같은데
I'm sure your friend's busy.
Has, uh, computers to fix.
- 우린 이만 갈까?
- 그래요
- Shall we?
- Sure.
척. 나 월드론 호텔에서 지내
Chuck, I'm staying at
the Hotel Waldron,
만나서 커피라도 한 잔 하자
so give me a call if you want
to grab a cup of coffee.
그래. 근데 내가 바빠서 말이야
시간 낼 수 있을지 볼게
Yeah, uh, well, you know,
I'm busy.
I'll check
with my people.
자네 예전 여자친구의 보스인
Your ex-girlfriend's boss,
기 르플뢰르는 콜 맥그레고르라는
유럽 제약회사 수석 연구원이네
Guy LeFleur, is the head
research scientist
for the European company
Cole-MacGregor Pharmaceuticals.
내 정보원에 따르면
생화학 무기를 만들어서
And my six has reports
that he may have developed a
bioweapon which he plans to sell
더 많은 값을 쳐주는 사람한테
팔 예정인 것 같다는 군
to the highest bidder.
질도 그 일에 관련됐나요?
Is Jill involved?
그게 바로
자네가 알아내야 할 일이야, 척
It's your job to find out,
Chuck.
케이시와 새라는
르플뢰르 박사를 감시하고
Casey and Sarah will surveil
Dr. LeFleur.
자넨 질과 다시
가까워져보게
We need you
to reconnect with Jill.
기에 대해서 알고 있는게
있는지 알아봐
Find out what she knows
about Guy.
네 그럴게요
Right, right, right, right.
가까워지라는건
메일을 보내거나
When you say "reconnect,"
you mean send her an e-mail
페이스북 친구 요청 같은걸
하라는 말씀이시죠?
or invite her to be
my new FaceBook friend, right?
그 호텔에 전화해서
데이트 약속을 잡으란 소리야
Call her at her hotel
and make a date.
질이 말하는거나
자네가 마주치는 사람들 중에
See if you flash
on anything she says
떠오르는게 있는지 보게
or anyone you meet.
죄송해요. 죄송한데요
데이트라뇨
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, a date
예전 여자친구랑요?
안 돼요. 장군님
with my ex?
No, General,
그건 진짜 끔찍한 생각이세요
that-that is
a terrible idea.
걔가 절 뻥 차버리고
망가뜨려놨어요
You see, she broke my heart.
She destroyed me.
걔 덕에 자신감도 운도
모두 잃었다고요
She took all
of my confidence,
my mojo.
- 운이 있긴 했어?
- 예전에는 있었어요
- You had mojo?
- I was on my way.
그리고 어쨌든
브라이스 라킨하고도 잤단 말이예요
Oh, and by the way,
she slept with Bryce Larkin.
안 그런 사람이 있나?
Hmm. Who hasn't?
척, 질이 당신한테
상처 줬다는거 알아요
Look, Chuck, I know
that Jill hurt you,
하지만 다시 만나보면
항상 원해 온 것처럼
but maybe seeing her again
will give you the closure
다 잊어버릴 수
있을지도 몰라요
that you've always wanted.
CIA를 위해서
열심히 해 줬으니까
You have done a
lot for the CIA,
이번엔 우리가 멋있게 만들어줄게요
and we're gonna make
you look good.
긍정적으로 생각해
Yeah, look on the bright side.
다시 운을
되찾을지도 모르잖아
Now you can get your mojo back.
Chuck 2x06
Chuck Versus the Ex
재커리 리바이
(척 바토스키 役)
이본느 스트라호브스키
(새라 워커 역 役)
조슈아 고메즈
(모건 그라임즈 役)
라이언 맥파틀린
(캡틴 짱 役)
마크 크리스토퍼 로렌스
(빅 마이크 役)
스캇 크린스키 / 빅 사하이
줄리아 링
새라 랜체스터
(엘리 바토스키 役)
아담 볼드윈
(존 케이시 役)
다들 알고 계시겠지만 오늘
우리의 소중한 매니저님을 잃을뻔했어요
As you already know we nearly
lost our dear leader today.
어떤 것에?
And to what?
겨우 조그만 도넛 조각에요
One tiny little carb-filled
donut.
도넛에 빅 마이크를 잃은지
몇 년 되지 않았어?
Please. We lost Big Mike
to donuts years ago?
실제로 불이나 지진같은
큰 재해가 일어났을 때
I shudder to think how people
like you would respond to
an actual catastrophe.
당신 같은 사람들이
어떻게 반응할지
생각하면 끔찍해요
A fire, an earthquake...
먼저 나가겠다고 전쟁을 치르겠죠
An all-out race war.
그래서 저와 마이크가
And that is why Michael
and I have decided
응급 상황 대처 수업을 마련했어요
to implement an emergency
preparedness course.
여러분의 동료가
가르쳐주실 분을 알고 있더군요
And it just so happens
that one of ur colleagues knew
someone willing to teach it.
안녕하세요, 여러분
Buenos dias, class.
정말 괜찮겠어요?
Hey, uh, you sure you
want to do this?
나 자원 봉사 좋아해, 척
I love volunteer work,
Chuck.
게다가 CPR은 별거 아니야
Besides,
CPR's a breeze.
꼬마 애들도 배울 수 있을걸
A child could learn it.
그래요. 한 번 해봐요
Well, then maybe
you have a shot.
다들 정말 좋은 선생님한테 배우는거야
Uh, hey, everybody,
you're in great hands.
나도 캡틴한테 배웠어
Awesome is who certified me.
이미 배웠을지도 모르지만, 척
You might be certified,
Chuck.
다른 사람들처럼
시험은 봐야해요
But you still have to take
the test like everyone else.
가자 로미오
데이트 갈 시간이야
Let's go, Romeo.
Time for your
big date.
CIA에서 너 멋있게 보여주려고
돈 많이 썼어
The CIA is shelling
out a lot to make you look good.
좋아요. 이 인형 세게 쳐 볼 사람?
Okay, so who's ready to pound
some plastic?
척
Hey!
Wow.
양복 새로 샀어?
New suit?
오늘 중요한 데이트 있나봐?
You have a big date?
그런거 아니야. 왜?
No big date. Why?
- 비싸보여서
- 아니 아니야
- Looks expensive.
- No, no, no, no.
싼 거야. 진짜 싼 거야
It was cheap.
Yeah, real cheap.
세일로 샀어
쿠폰이 있었거든
It was on sale.
- I had a coupon.
- Uh-huh.
새라때문에 이렇게까지
차려 입다니 정말 귀엽다
I think it's cute you get
all dressed up for Sarah.
새라는 운도 좋아
She's lucky.
저기 누나
Hey, sis.
응?
- Hmm?
- Um...
예전 남자친구
더그 월드 생각 해본적 있어?
do you ever think about your
ex-boyfriend, Doug Wald?
아니. 왜?
No. Why?
어쩌다가 누나랑
더그랑 마주쳤다고 생각해봐
Let's say
totally randomly old Dougie,
you know, you guys ran
into each other
오랜만에 밥 한 끼 먹자면
어떻게 하겠어?
and he asked you out to dinner
to catch up
on old times?
What would you say?
글쎄 아마 좋다고 하겠지
I guess theoretically,
I'd say yes.
그렇게 생각한다니 다행이다
I am so glad you said that.
You see,
사실 나 새라 만나러 가는거 아니야
I-I'm not going out
with Sarah tonight,
질 만나기로 했어
I'm actually going out
with Jill.
질이라고? 안돼!
Jill?! No!
안돼 안돼!
No, no, no!
절대 안돼!
Absolutely not!
방금 더그 얘기할 땐
괜찮다고 했잖아?
What, what about what you
just said about Doug?
그 얘긴 다 잊어버려, 응?
Just forget
what I just said, okay?
널 차 버리고 상처주고
There is no scenario
in which you should
네 제일 친한 친구랑 잔
be going to dinner
with the girl that dumped you,
여자애하고 저녁을 왜 먹어
broke your heart and slept
with your best friend.
척. 그런데 양복을 사?
Chuck, you bought a new suit?
싸게 주고 산거라니까
I told you, coupon.
척
Chuck...
누난 지나치게 난리치는
누나가 안 되려고 노력 중이야
look, I'm trying not to be
the overprotective big sister.
누나가 난리를 쳐? 아니야
You? Never.
난 걔가 너한테
얼마나 상처를 준지 아니까
It's just that I know
that she hurt you, you know?
다시 그런 일이
생길까봐 그래
I don't want to see you go
through that again.
하지만...
But...
클러치가 꿈쩍을 않네
Sticky clutch.
내 비서한테 고치라고 해야겠다
Remind me to have my
assistant to have that fixed.
주차 요원은 저 쪽에
있는 것 같은데?
I think the valet's
up a little further.
날씨도 좋은데 조금 걸을까?
Beautiful night
for a walk, huh?
Shall we?
자 좋아
Okay. Here we go.
고마워요
Thank you.
안녕하세요 바토스키 씨
Hey, Bartowski.
어서오세요 / 고맙습니다
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
오래 기다리신건 아니겠죠?
이쪽입니다
Hope you haven't been
waiting long. Right this way.
안녕하세요
Hey.
안녕하십니까
Hello, sir.
안녕하세요
네 안녕하세요
Hello. Yeah, hello.
안녕하세요
Hi.
오늘 멋있으시네요
바토스키 씨
Looking good, Mr. Bartowski.
멋있어요
Looking good.
모두 다 CIA 사람들이예요?
Is everyone in here CIA?
물론이지
Of course.
고마워요
고맙습니다
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
수고했어요 조나단
Huh, thank you
Jonathan.
와 나 놀랐어
Wow, I'm impressed.
네가 이 곳 주인이라도 되는 것 같아
It's like you own the place.
아니 아니야
주인은 무슨
No, no, no,
God no.
그냥 여기에 투자를 좀 했거든
Just, uh, just an investor.
내가 뭘 어쩌겠어?
I mean, what can I say?
내가 원래 송아지 요리에 약하잖아
I'm a sucker
for a good veal parm.
안녕하세요 바토스키 씨
Good evening,
Mr. Bartowski.
두 분, 마실 것은
어떤 것로 드릴까요?
Can I get
you two anything to drink?
항상 드시던건 어떠세요?
The usual perhaps?
레 피에프 드 라그랑쥬
2000년산이요
A 2000 Les Fiefs de Lagrange.
네 좋아요
Oui, oui.
네가 이렇게 잘 돼서 다행이야, 척
I'm really glad
things turned out
so well for you, Chuck.
그런.. 일이 있었는데도 말이야
Especially after,
you know, what happened.
그래. 그 일 말인데..
Yeah, uh... about that.
질, 나 시험지 훔친적 없어
Um, Jill,
I-I never stole those tests.
지금와서 그게 뭐가 중요하겠어
Well, uh,
that doesn't matter now.
그래 지금이야 그렇지
Sure, it doesn't matter now.
지금은 멋있는 이탈리아 차도 몰고
You know, now that I drive
a fine Italian automobile
이 레스토랑에서도
유명할 정도가 됐으니까
and I'm alarmingly
well-known
at this
particular restaurant,
하지만 난 그 때
네가 날 믿어주길 바랬어
but I needed you to believe me
when it did matter.
이젠 네 말 믿어
I do believe you,
Chuck, and...
그 때도 널 믿었어야 했을지도 모르지
maybe I should've
believed you at Stanford.
하지만 시험지가
네 방에서 발견됐고
But the tests
were in your room
브라이스도 네가
컨닝을 했다는데
and Bryce said
you were cheating.
내가 어떻게 네 말을
믿을 수 있었겠어?
What was I supposed
to think at the time?
그래. 브라이스가 네가
날 뻥 차버리고
Yeah, Bryce must've made a very
convincing argument
걔 침대로 뛰어들만큼
설득력있게 얘기했겠지
for you to dump me and then
hop right into his bed.
이렇게 만나는게
좋은 생각이 아니었나보다
Maybe this
wasn't such a good idea.
대화 중에 죄송합니다
바토스키 씨
I'm sorry to interrupt,
Mr. Bartowski,
바에 바토스키씨께
전화가 왔습니다
but there's a phone call
for you at the bar.
잠시만
Excuse me.
대체 무슨 짓을 하는거예요?
What do you think
you're doing?
접고 잊어버리려는거죠
Getting closure.
왜 그랬던건지 쟤가
나한테 얘길 해줘야 하잖아요
She owes me
an explanation.
아니 전혀
No, she doesn't.
널 차려고 수정 헌법 1조를 행사한거야
(언론·신문·종교의 자유를 보장한 조항)
She exercised her First
Amendment right to dump you.
다시 자리로 돌아가서
기가 꾸미는게 뭔지 알아내
Now get back in there and find
out what Guy is planning.
척. 힘들다는거 다 알아요
Look, Chuck,
I know it's hard,
하지만 오늘 밤엔
스파이로써 행동해줘요
but tonight, you have
to be a spy first.
네 힘들어요
난 새라 같은 사람이 아니예요
Yeah, it is hard.
I'm not like you, Sarah.
로봇처럼 내 감정을 껐다 켰다
맘대로 할 수가 없다고요
I can't turn my emotions
on and off like some robot.
미안해요
엉뚱한 말이 튀어나왔네요
I'm sorry,
that was uncalled for.
오늘 내가 왜 이러는지 모르겠네요
I'm not acting
like myself tonight.
스스로 동정하는거 끝났어요?
Are you done feeling sorry
for yourself?
10분, 15분정도
나 혼자 애처롭게 지내고 싶지만
Personally, I'd like
another ten to 15 minutes
of really pathetic
self-indulgence,
일은 해야겠죠
다시 가 볼게요
but duty calls.
I'm going back in.
고마워요
Thanks.
미안해
이젠 자리 뜨는 일 없을거야
Sorry about that.
No more interruptions.
약속할게. 어쨌든
I promise,
and, uh, by the way,
몇 분전에 여기
앉아있던 남자 말이야
that guy who was just sitting
here a couple minutes ago.
기억하지?
척 바토스키랑 똑같이 생긴 사람
You remember him? Looked just
like Chuck Bartowski?
투덜대고 짜증부렸던 남자말이야
He was a little whiny
and bitter?
알고 보니까 그 사람 사기꾼이래
Turns out,
he's an imposter.
그래? / 응 그렇대
이젠 걱정마
- Really?
- Yeah, really, but don't worry about it,
내가 방금 바에서
쿵푸로 혼쭐내고 왔거든
'cause I just kung fu'd
him at the bar,
그니까 오늘 그 사람이
널 괴롭히는 일은 없을거야
and he won't be bothering you
for the rest of the evening.
잘됐다
Oh, I'm glad,
이 척 바토스키가
훨씬 마음에 들거든
'cause I like this
Chuck Bartowski a lot more.
나도
Me, too.
맞다 그러고 보니
네 직업 얘길 못 들었네
So, uh,
you never told me
exactly what
you were working on.
그 얘긴 해줄수가 없어
Oh, uh, I can't
really talk about it.
이상하게 들리지, 나도 알아
That sounds mysterious, I know.
그래서 요즘엔 이상한 사람들이
관련된 일이 아닌가 싶기도 해
I'm starting to think there are
some sketchy people involved.
별일 아닐지도 모르지만
I'm probably just
being paranoid.
누굴 믿어야할지 모르겠어
I just, I don't know
who to trust.
난 믿어도 돼
You can trust me.
생화학 기억나?
Remember biochem?
우린 인플루엔자의 변형을 연구중이야
We're working
on a strain of influenza,
specifically
특히 헤마글루티닌이 어떻게
바이러스성 외피를
액포막과 융합시키는지 말이야
how the hemagglutinin protein
fuses the viral envelope
with the vacuole's membrane.
무슨 소린지
하나도 못 알아들었지?
Did that sound like
total gibberish?
"생화학 기억나?" 부분은
확실하게 이해했는데
I understood completely,
"Do you remember biochem?"
그 다음 부분은 하나도
못 알아 들었어
And then everything
after that was a little fuzzy.
알았어. 간단하게 얘기해줄게
Okay, I'll simplify.
야 찰스!
Yo, Charles!
안녕 친구
Hey, buddy.
그 여자 분은 누구야?
Who's the babe?
처음엔 새라더니
이번엔 조그만 이 섹시한 여자야?
First Sarah,
now this Chiquita banana?
우리랑 공유할 생각 없어?
만나서 반갑습니다
When are you going to start sharing the wealth, buddy?
Nice to meet you.
새라가 누구야?
Who's, uh, Sarah?
네 친구들이야?
And, um, are these
friends of yours?
아니 아니야. 쟤넨 그냥
바이모어에서 만난
No. No, they're just
old, old Buy More
애들인데 아직도
연락하고 지내고 있어
colleagues that
haven't moved on.
가, 빨리 가라고
Move on. Move on.
- 여기 차 가져왔습니다
- 고맙습니다
- Your car, sir.
- Oh, thank you.
와 저거 누구 페라리야?
Whoa! Whose Ferrari?
네 차 아니였어?
This isn't your car?
이 친구, 바이모어에서
시간당 12달러 50센트 받아요
Um, the guy makes $12.50
an hour at the Buy More.
계산해 보세요
You do the math, sister.
아직 바이모어에서
일하는거야, 척?
You still work
at the Buy More, Chuck?
응 일해
Yes, I do.
그래 컴퓨터 분야에서
일 한다면서?
You do. What about your
computer business?
바이모어에서는 하드웨어나
다른 것도 많이 팔거든..
Technically, the Buy More
offers a wide range
of hardware
and other things...
스탠포드가 문, 이과를
동시에 인정해줬으면 좋았을텐데
Wow, too bad Stanford
doesn't offer a BA in BS,
그럼 네가
빨리 졸업했을거 아니야
'cause you could've
graduated early.
질, 가지마!
잠시만!
Jill, please don't!
Look, I'm not--
전부 다 거짓말은 아니였어!
it's not all a lie!
내가 다 설명할게
I can explain to you...
찰스. 우리가 일부러 그런건...
Charles, we did not mean
to bust your whole little...
닥치고 집에나 가!
Just go home!
그렇지 잘한다!
몸을 더 움직여!
That's it.
Attaboy, work the body!
더 움직여! 더 움직이라고!
Work the body, kid.
Work the body!
안녕. 난 새라야
척의 섹시한 금발 여자친구지
Hi, I'm Sarah, Chuck's
hot, blonde girlfriend.
난 척의 섹시한
갈색 머리 친구야
And I'm Chuck's
smoking hot brunette.
나쁜년! / 이 년이!
- Bitch.
- Slut.
해결 할 방법은 하나뿐이야
There's only one way
to settle this.
베개싸움! / 베개싸움!
- Pillow fight!
자 여러분 다들 연습은...
Okay, so how's everyone
coming with the chest...?
You're a dirty girl.
그만해요
Come on, guys.
다들 뭐가 문제예요?
What's wrong with you?
전 술을 너무 많이 마셔요
I drink too much.
저희 부모님은 기준이 너무 높으세요
My parents had
impossible standards.
자 진지하게 해 봅시다
Well, let's get serious.
내일 시험은 어떻게
통과하려고 그래요?
How do you expect to pass
the exam tomorrow?
시험? 뭐라고요?
Exam? Come again?
에밋씨가 필기 시험이 있다고
말 안 해주시던가요?
Emmett didn't tell you about
the written part
of the test?
내가 시험 보는걸 좋아했으면
Man, if I wanted
to take tests,
지금쯤 배 선장이 되 있을걸요
I would've been
a boat captain.
만약에 통과 못 하면 어떻게 돼요?
So what happens
if we don't pass?
형편 없는 일자리 구해서
어디 산 골짜기에서
We get lousy jobs
and live a small,
별 볼일없는 인생을 사는거지
아이고 무서워라
under-realized life
in the Valley; ooh, scary.
아니면 30시간동안
급여도 못 받고
Or you can take
the 30-hour remedial course,
직접 시간 내서
보충 수업을 들어도 되고요
unpaid,
and on your own time.
이제야 다들 집중한 것 같네요
의사 선생님
Oh, that seemed
to get their attention.
Doctor...
뜨거, 아 뜨거
Hot, hot...
모르는 척 할까?
Am I supposed to ignore you
아님 네가 꼭 대답해야하는
몇 가지 사적인 질문을 해도 될까?
or can I ask you a series
of personal questions
that you have to answer?
누나 말이 맞았어
You were right.
누나 말은 항상 옳아
You're always right.
어제 질하고
데이트 하는게 아니였어
I never should've gone out
with Jill last night.
척, 누나가
과민반응 한 걸지도 몰라
Chuck, maybe I overreacted.
질하고 저녁을 먹어야 할
이유가 있었을지도 모르는데
You know? Maybe there
was a reason
to go to dinner
with Jill.
응. 나한테
망신 좀 주려고
Yeah, to humiliate myself.
너희 둘 헤어질 때
엄청나게 궁금한 점은 많았는데
Come on,
the way things ended
with you guys,
you've always had a million
해답은 전혀 없었잖아
이젠 몇 가지 해답은 얻었고
questions and no answers,
and now you finally got some.
그래서?
So what?
과거사를 쑤셔놔서
나한테 좋을게 뭐가 있어?
What good did it do me to go
poking around in my past?
왜냐하면 이젠
그 모든 궁금증과
Because maybe now,
'만약의' 얘긴 그만두고
without all
that wondering
그 시절을 잊어버릴 수 있을지도 모르잖아
and what-iffing,
you can finally
close that chapter of your life.
또 맞는 소리하네
Right again.
뉴욕 스테이크로
중간 정도 구워주세요
New York steak, medium rare.
1104호입니다
Room 1104.
기가 방금 룸 서비스를 주문했어
Guy just ordered room service.
응
Hmm...
진정해요 다들
나예요
Easy, easy, hey.
- 저 싸우러 온 거 아니예요
- 네가 여긴 뭣하러 와?
- I come in peace.
- What the hell are you doing here?
그냥 질은 괜찮은가 싶어서 들렀어요
I thought I'd swing by
and, you know,
check up on Jill;
make sure she's doing all right.
질은 잘 있어요, 척
She's fine, Chuck.
어제 방에 들어가서
한 번도 안 나왔어요
She came home last night and she
hasn't left her room since.
잠깐 잠깐. 조용히 해봐
Wait, wait-- shh!
전화 걸고 있어
She's making a call.
OUTPUT
MUTE
여보세요?
Hello?
망할. 도청기가 고장났어
Damn, bug's on the fritz.
새 걸로 바꿔야겠다
We need a new one.
근무자인척 들어가서
새로 심고 올게
I'll go in as housekeeping
and plant another.
레스토랑에서 주문받았으니까
알아 볼지도 몰라
She might recognize you
as the waitress
from the restaurant.
내가 진정제를 놓을게
I'll just tranq her.
1시간이면 아무것도
기억 못 하고 일어날거야
She'll wake up in an hour,
thinking ?thing of it.
아니요 잠시만요
Whoa, whoa, whoa--
hey, hey.
제가 갈게요, 제가
I'll go. I'll go.
어제 일 사과하고
I'll apologize for last night,
걘 내가 얼마나
형편 없는 놈인지 얘기하면서
she'll tell me what a giant
loser I am,
도청기 심을테니깐
안정제는 필요 없어요
and I'll plant the new bug;
no tranqing necessary.
방법 알죠, 척?
You know where
it goes, Chuck?
바닥에 버튼이 있어요
One button
on the bottom,
누르면 켜지고
다시 누르면 꺼져요
click on, click off.
알았어요
All right.
들어갈게요
I'm going in.
들어갈게. 내가 가서
시험지 갖고 나올테니까
I'M GOING IN.
Allow me between six and eight minutes
그동안 6분에서
8분정도 시간을 벌어봐
to get in,
grab the test and get out.
다들 준비됐지?
Are you guys ready?
태어날 때부터 난 이미 준비됐어
I was born ready.
난 태어날 때부터 모자랐어
I was born premature.
시작하자
Showtime.
안녕하세요
Hey.
척 집에 없어. 미안
Chuck's not here, sorry.
잠깐 잠시만요
저희도 알아요
No-no-no-no-no
we know.
저희도 알아요
We know, we know,
Elizabeth.
그래서 척에 대해서
얘기 좀 할까해서 왔어요
That's why we're here,
to talk to you
about Chuck.
캡틴 가방이다
Awesome's bag.
찰스가 최근 들어 뭔가..
Has Charles been
acting a little, um...
이상하게 굴지 않던가요?
strange lately?
아니
평소랑 똑같던데. 왜?
No. No more than usual, why?
척이 광견병에 걸린 것 같아요
We think Chuck
might have rabies.
그 병의 징후가 보여요
All the signs
are there:
정신착란에 예민하고
오늘 점심 때는
bouts of confusion,
general edginess,
and at lunch,
제프가 척 입 주변에
거품이 있는 걸 봤대요
Jeff here thought
he saw some foam
around his mouth.
그래 걱정해줘서 고맙다
Okay, I appreciate the concern.
잘 가
Good-bye.
이런
Oh, no.
뭘 찾고 계신가?
Looking for something?
내가 이걸 가방에 둘거라고
생각한건 아니지?
You didn't think I'd leave this
in my bag, did you?
방금 무슨 일이 있었는지..
Honey, you won't
believe what I just...
모건. 지금 들고 있는거
내 속옷이야?
Morgan, are you
holding my underwear?
잠시만요 잠시만요
Wait a second, wait a second.
정말 확실하게 얘기하는데
Wait, I-I need to be
very clear about this.
제가 여기 온 건 CPR 시험때문에
Okay, the only
thing I came
시험지를 훔치러 온 거예요
in here to steal was
a CPR test.
그러니까 절 변태 취급하고
누나 팬티..를 가지러 왔냐는 말은
So any suggestions
to anything pervy-related
to your panties...
panties--
underpants
정말 정말 하지 마세요
is, frankly, outrageous.
그니깐 지금 변태는 아니라면서
So you deny being a perv,
도둑인건 인정한다는거야?
but you admit
to being a thief?
적어도 솔직했잖아요?
Do I at least get points
for honesty?
누구세요?
Who is it?
어제 페라리 빌리고 거짓말했지만
It's the lying,
yet well-meaning fool
나쁜 뜻은 전혀 없었던 바보야
who rented a Ferrari
last night.
문 안 열어준다에 10달러건다
Ten bucks says she doesn't
open the door for him.
20달러로 해
Make it $20 and you're on.
너랑 얘기하고 싶지 않아, 척
I don't want to talk
to you, Chuck.
그래 그럼
Okay, well, then,
얘긴 내가 할게
I'll do all the talking.
네가 놀랄지도 모르겠지만
I know this may come
as a shock to you,
정말 미친짓하러 왔어
사실대로 말할게
but I'm here to do something
totally crazy
and tell you the truth.
그래 나 아직
바이모어에서 일해
I still work
at the Buy More
그리고 아직도
우리 누나랑 같이 살고
and, uh, I still live
with my sister,
그리고 여전히 앞으로
뭘 하고 살지 결정 못 했어
and I still have no idea
what I'm doing with my life.
네가 날 뭔가
특별한 사람이라고
I guess I just wanted you
to think
생각해주길 바랬나봐
I was someone special, so...
그래서 밖에 나가서
새 양복도 사고
in order to accomplish that,
I went out and got a new suit
어떻게 운전하는지도 모르는
차까지 빌린거야
and rented a car
that I clearly
have no idea
how to drive,
왜냐하면 널 다시 만났던 그 순간
because from the second
I saw you again,
내가 아직도
널 잊지 못 했다는걸 꺠달았거든
I knew that I hadn't
gotten over you yet, Jill.
정말?
Really?
나 아직 못 잊었어?
You haven't gotten over me?
응
No.
들어와
Get in here.
방이 더럽지, 미안해
Sorry about the mess.
그 강연을 준비하느라고 이래
Still working on the lecture.
괜찮아. 네가
어제 말해준거 말이야
Yeah, you
were starting
to say last night...
전염병이었나 뭐 그런거
infectious disease or something.
꼭 네가 아람말로
얘기하는 것 같더라
I don't know, it sounded
like you were speaking Aramaic.
그런거 아니야
Not Aramaic.
생화학 입문이잖아
Simple biochem 101.
아 맞다
Oh, right.
너 그 시간에 자서 모르지
You slept through that class
in college.
어차피 물건 파는데엔
그런거 필요없잖아
Lot of good that would do me
in my current line of work.
그만해
StOP it!
뭘 그만해?
Stop what?
널 깔아 뭉게는거 그만해, 척
Stop underselling
yourself, Chuck.
어젯밤에 말이야
There was a part
of last night,
네 차가 중간에 멈춘 다음부터
somewhere after getting
minor whiplash in your car
내가 널 도로 한복판에
두고 떠나기 전까지
and before abandoning you
on the side of the road,
where I had a really,
나 네 덕에 정말 즐거웠어
really nice time.
정말?
Really?
응. 그러니까
거짓말은 그만해
Yes... so no more lies.
더이상 하지마, 알았지?
No more
deception, okay?
알았어. 다신 안 할게
No more lies, no more deception.
좋아
Good.
내가 이걸 얼마나 그리워했는지 알아?
Do you know how much
I missed doing this?
뭘 말이야?
Missed doing what?
어떻게 됐어요?
What happened?
네?
Huh? Oh.
네, 아니, 그게..
정말 좋았어요. 네
Yeah, no, it was...
it was great, fine.
우리 둘이 맘이 통했어요
We really connected.
도청기 얘기하는거야 멍청아
She's talking
about the bug, moron.
아 그거요
Oh, that.
네 물론이죠
심어놨어요
Yes, of course, that,
I planted it.
심어뒀어요
It is planted.
근데 안 켜놓은것 같기도 하고...
I may have turned it off,
though-- I'm not...
왜 그랬어요?
Why would you do that?
괜찮아. 멍청이가 쓸까봐서
다 준비를 해뒀으니까
Relax, these things are
pretty much idiot-proof.
도청기가 방에만 있으면
신호를 잡아낼거야
If it's in the room, it
picks up the signal.
켜졌어. 이제 핸드폰이랑
전화기 모두 들을 수 있어
It worked,
we're tapped in
to her cell and
the room phone.
왜 그렇게 웃어요?
Why are you smiling like that?
질이 키스했어요
She kissed me.
스파이도 아니고 거짓말도 안했고
그냥 나인데도요
No spy stuff, no lies, just me.
암호명 : 울프 덴
CODE NAME: WOLF DEN
저기 저 남자, 암호명이
울프 덴인 암살자예요
Oh! Uh, that dude is some kind
of an assassin--
his code name
is Wolf Den.
11층이잖아
기 방이 그 층에 있어
11-- that's Guy's floor.
척 / 네, 알아요
- Chuck...
- Yeah, I know, I know.
- 밴 안에 있으라고요
- 아무것도 만지지마
- Stay in the van.
- Don't touch anything.
Ow!
룸 서비스입니다
Room service, sir.
이쪽에 두고 가세요
Just put it over here.
여보세요?
HELLO?
응. 나야 질
Hey, it's Jill.
어제 그 일 어떻게 됐어?
How are you
after last night?
맙소사, 쉐리. 있잖아?
OH MY GOD, SHARI, GUESS WHAT?
오늘 사과한다고
내 방에 찾아왔더라고
You're not gonna
believe who came
to my room to apologize tonight.
뭐? 설마 방에
들여 보내준건 아니겠지
WHAT? Please tell me you didn't
let that loser in.
꼭 강아지 같은 얼굴을 하고 있어서
Well, he looked
like a puppy dog.
안 된다고 할 수가 없었어
I couldn't say no.
그리고 여전히 귀엽더라고
And... I still think
he's kind of cute.
귀여워? 컴퓨터 만지면서
한 시간에 겨우 10달러 버는 애야
Cute? He's a
computer dork
that makes
ten bucks an hour.
이봐 12달러 50센트거든
Hello...
it's $12.50.
척?
Chuck?
척, 이게 무슨 일이야?
Chuck, are you
on my phone?
질, 너니?
Uh, Jill, is that you?
어떻게 네 목소리가 들려?
Why are you on my phone?
글쎄 나도 모르겠어
그게.. 그게..
I don't know, I don't know.
It's so... it's...
너한테 전화 걸고 있었거든
I tried calling you, so I...
아마... 전화가 혼선됐나봐
I think our... our wires
got crossed or something.
이거 공동 회선이야?
Is this a party line?
내 전화기에 무슨 짓을 한거야?
도청기라도 심었어?
What did you do to my phone?
Did you bug it or something?
뭐? 내가 곤충학자라도 돼?
(Bug : 곤충, 도청기)
Bug it? What... what am I,
an entomologist?
아니야. 무슨
말도 안 되는 소릴 하는거야
No, you're...
you're talking crazy jargon.
경비 부를거야
I'm calling security.
Oh, oh, oh.
안에서 잠겼어
It's bolted on the inside.
열어
Go.
클리어
Clear.
척, 방 안에 기가 없어
Chuck, Guy is not in his room.
저도 알아요
I know.
맘껏 우세요
Let it all out.
고맙습니다
Thank you.
마음이 안 좋아요
I feel terrible.
안에 들어가서 위로해줘야겠어요
Maybe I should
go in there
and console her.
질이 당신이
스파이라는걸 알아선 안 돼요, 척
She can't know
you're a spy, Chuck.
당연하죠. 스토커라고
생각할테니까요
Of course, she'll just
think I'm a stalker.
그렇게 생각 안해요
She doesn't think
you're a stalker.
그럼...
So...
기 씨가 살해당할만한
이유를 알고 계신가요?
Why do you think Guy was killed?
여긴 대체 어디죠?
What is this place?
눈은 왜 가린거예요?
Why was I blindfolded?
여긴 CIA 비밀 기지입니다
It's a secret
CIA compound.
로버트 양, 우린
지난 며칠간 당신을 지켜봤어요
We've been watching you
for days, Ms. Roberts.
절 지켜봐요? 왜요?
Watching me? Why?
우린 당신 보스, 기씨가
We thought
your boss, Guy,
수상한 일에 연루되어있다고 생각해요
was into some shady business.
그래서 당신을 보호하기 위해서
지켜본 겁니다
We kept an eye on you, as well.
To protect you.
제 예전 남자친구 척이예요
That's my ex-boyfriend, Chuck.
척도 이 일과 관련되어있나요?
Is he involved in this?
갑자기 이상하게 굴었거든요
He's been acting
really weird lately.
정말 정상적인 것 같다가도
One minute,
he's completely normal.
갑자기 완전 미친사람처럼 굴더라고요
The next, he's acting
like total lunatic.
스토커 같다고는 안 했잖아요
She didn't
say stalker.
꼭 스토커처럼요
Almost like a stalker.
패배자 같은 녀석들은
다들 그래요
Yeah, it can be a pattern
with these losers.
예쁜 여자가 웃어만 주면
홀랑 넘어가는거죠
A pretty girl smiles at them,
they get all infatuated.
그런 경우 수도없이 봤어요
Seen it a
million times.
어쨌든 아니예요
관련없어요
No.
He wasn't involved.
하지만, 기 씨는...
Your boss, Guy, however...
기 씨가 관련되어 있을지도 모르지만
요원님이 생각하는 그런건 아니예요
Maybe Guy was involved,
but not how you think.
기 씨가 생화학 무기에 쓰이는
변형된 인플루엔자를 발견했어요
Guy had discovered ???
for a strain of influenza
used in a bioweapon,
공기로 운반되는 인플루엔자라
정말 치명적이고
an airborne influenza so deadly
누출되면 한시간내에
사람을 죽일수도 있어요
it could kill a person
within one hour if exposed.
근데 며칠 전에,
기씨가 우리 회사에서
Now, a couple
of days ago,
Guy learned that
our company
비밀리에 그 인플루엔자
생화학 무기를 팔아 왔다는걸 알게 됐어요
secretly sells
the influenza bioweapon.
그래서 기씨가 회의에서
우리 연구 결과를 발표하려던거예요
That's why Guy
planned to present
our research at the convention,
우리 회사에서 더이상
그 사실을 숨기지 못하도록요
so that the company couldn't
cover it up any more.
이젠 제가 해야겠죠
I guess it's up to me
to do that now.
안돼 안돼 안돼
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
그럼 로버트양께서 발표를 하시고..
So, you'll do the
presentation...
안돼요, 케이시!
너무 위험해요!
No, it's too
dangerous, Casey!
저기, 누가 두드리는데요
Um, your window's knocking.
실례할게요
Excuse me.
뭐야? / 질이 발표하면 안돼요
- What?
- Jill is not going to the conference.
암살자가 죽이려 들거예요
THE ASSASIN WILL KILL HER.
기회는 이것뿐이야
It's our only chance,
그 자를 불러내려면
이 방법밖에 없어
the only way
to smoke him out.
질한테 너무 위험하잖아요!
It is too dangerous
for her, all right?
제 입장은 단호해요
I am putting my foot down.
조심스럽게요
Gingerly.
바토스키. 내 임무는
모든 시민들을 지키는거야
Look, Bartowski,
my job is to look after
all the citizens
of this nation,
겨우 네 여자 하나가 아니고
not just the girl
that raises your flag.
새라 제발요
질을 미끼로 쓰면 안돼요
Sarah...
please, we can't
use Jill as bait
그 발표를 하는건 너무 위험해요
and risk her life
giving that presentation.
좋아요. 그럼 발표는 내가 할게요
Fine, I'll give
the presentation.
척 어디갔어?
Where's Chuck?
제프, 척 금방 올거야
Jeff, he will be here, okay?
잘만 하면 척 모르게
답 베낄 수 있을거야
And as long
as we play this cool,
we can cheat
off of Chuck,
and he'll never know,
all right?
걘 CPR에 대해서
모르는게 없어
He knows the CPR stuff
inside and out.
그건 그렇지만, 모건
만약에 걔가 안 오면
Yeah, but Morgan,
if he doesn't show,
우린.. / 누가 안 와요?
- we are in...
- If who doesn't show?
내가 맞춰볼까요
툭하면 늦는 척 말이군요
Oh, let me guess: the
perennially tardy Chuck.
안녕 안녕
늦어서 미안해요
Hi, hi,
sorry I'm late.
아니야. 딱 맞춰 왔어
Oh, you're right
on time, bro.
Hey.
Yeah, no problem.
흥미롭군요
That was interesting.
시험은 한 시간동안 이뤄집니다
You have one hour
to take the test.
자 그럼...
You may begin...
시작하세요
...now.
Oh, no, that's
not right.
No, of course not.
어때?
Anything?
아직까진 아무도 없어
It's all good so far.
모두 착석해 주세요
Please take your seats.
르플뢰르 박사님이
하기로 하셨던 발표는
Giving the presentation
for Dr. Lafleur
will be... his associate
호주, 시드니에서 오신 동료
에바 앤더슨 박사님께서 대신 하시겠습니다
coming from Sydney, Australia,
Dr. Eva Anderson.
감사합니다
Thank you.
네 안녕하세요
저는 이바 앤더슨 박사입니다
Yes, g'day,
I'm Dr. Eva Anderson,
전 여러분께
인문과학 분야를 바꿀
and d I'm here to talk
to you all today
매우 치명적인 독성 물질에 대해
about a deadly poison
that could change
말씀드리려 이 자리에 섰습니다
the course of human science.
이렇게 르플뢰르 박사님을 대신하여
I'm honored to stand
before you all today
on behalf of Dr. Lafleur.
발표를 할 수 있게 되어 영광입니다
지난 몇 년간의 연구를 통해...
Throughout the many years
of our research...
실례합니다
화장실에 가야겠어요
Um, excuse me,
I've got to go to the loo.
문을 봉쇄해! 어서!
Seal the room, seal the room!
여러분 NSA 응급 상황입니다
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is an NSA emergency.
누구도, 그 누구도
출입을 할 수 없습니다
No one-- I repeat, no one--
gets in or out.
죄송해요 죄송합니다
Sorry, sorry.
죄송한데요
이 전화는 꼭 받아야해서요
Oh, um, I'm sorry,
I have to take this.
중요한 전화일지도 몰라요
This could be
an important call.
그럼 이건 안 중요하단 소립니까?
Oh, I'm sorry,
and this isn't important?
시험이 끝나기 전까진
절대 나갈 수 없어요
There is no leaving the room
during the test.
케이시, 여보세요
무슨 일 있어요?
Casey, hey,
everything okay?
울프 덴이 독을 누출시켰어
Our Wolf Den friend
released the poison.
새라는 빠져나갔는데
Sarah got out.
난 아직 과학자들하고 갇혀있어
I'm still in here
with the scientists.
위험 물질 처리반이 오고 있긴 한데
Hazmat crews are on their way.
한 시간 정도밖에 여유가 없어
We have an hour, maybe less.
빨리 질한테 가서
해독제를 갖고 있는지 봐
You gotta get to Jill.
See if she has an antidote.
지금 당장은 질이 절
보고싶어하지 않을 것 같은데요
Um, I... I really don't
think she wants
to see me right now.
척, 우리 다 죽어간다고
Chuck, we're dying here.
무슨 말을 하든, 무슨 짓을 하든
상관없으니까 어서 가봐
I don't care what you have
to say or do, just get it done.
가야겠어
시험 잘 봐
Gotta go, good luck.
생명을 구하는게
중요하지 않은 모양이지
I guess someone
doesn't think
saving lives
is important.
PUSH
질, 나 척이야
빨리 문 좀 열어봐
Jill, it's Chuck,
you have to open the door!
그냥 가, 척
Go away, Chuck!
더이상 재미 없으니까
This isn't funny
anymore.
지금 긴급상황이야, 알겠어?
Look, it's an emergency, okay?
나에 대한 신용도가
땅에 떨어진건 아는데
I know that my credibility
with you is at an all-time low
내 얘기 좀 들어봐
but you need to listen to me.
생화학 무기가
컨퍼런스 센터에 누출됐어
The bioweapon has been released
at the conference center.
네가 그 무길 어떻게 알아?
How do you know
about the virus?
왜냐하면, 질..
Because, Jill...
내가 CIA 요원이니까
...I'm a CIA agent.
세상에. 척, 너 정말
어디 가서 도움 좀 받아야겠다
Oh, my God, Chuck, you really
need to get some help.
내가 그 도움이야
I am the help.
내가 지금까지 말했던건 믿지마
Don't believe anything else
that I've told you,
하지만 이건 믿어
지금 당장 해독제가 필요해
but believe this. We have to get
them the antidote right now.
자꾸 이러면 경찰 부를거야, 척
I'm going to call the police,
Chuck.
내가 이미 불렀어
I've already taken the liberty.
네가 직접 봐
Have a look for yourself.
세상에
Oh, my God.
사실이었구나
You are telling the truth.
기다려
Hold on.
꽤 귀엽지 않아요?
She's pretty cute, right?
예전에 사겼었어요
We used to date.
됐어 / 그래
- Okay.
내 가까이 있어
겁먹지 말고
Look, ju stay close,
don't be scared.
자 여러분 출발하죠
All right, people, wheels up.
갑시다!
Let's move!
저기요!
Hey!
여기 책임자가 누구죠?
Who's in charge here?
전데요
I am.
더이상 아닙니다
Not anymore.
고마워요
Thank you.
케이시, 척이예요
Casey, it's Chuck.
지금 질하고 같이 있어요
좀 어때요?
I'm with Jill.
What's your status?
15분정도 남았어
By my time,
we got about 15 minutes.
내가 들어가야해
I have to go in there.
지금 당장 A등급 보호복이 필요해요
Okay, I need a Level A
Hazmat suit right now.
아직 보호복이
준비되지 않았습니다
don't have
those suits yet.
10분후면 질병 관리 본부가 도착할거예요
CDC will be here
in ten minutes.
지금 10분이나 여유 없어요
We don't have ten minutes.
그럼 안 입고 들어가겠어요
I'll go in without one.
안돼
네가? 안돼
No. You? No.
너무 위험해
내가 들어갈게
It's too dangerous.
I'll do it.
척. 저 안에 들어가려면
Chuck, whoever goes in there
해독제를 만들 줄 알아야해
그건 나뿐이잖아
has to be able to make
the antidote. That's me.
네가 말해주면
내가 할 수 있을까?
Well, is it something
you could talk me through?
그럴지도 모르지
I guess.
그래. 그렇다면 내가 갈게
Okay, well,
then I'm going in.
안돼 척, 잠시만!
No, Chuck, wait!
정말 들어갈거야?
Are you sure?
응
Yeah.
들어갈거야
I'm sure.
알겠어
Okay.
좋아 그럼 일단
주사부터 맞아야해
Okay, uh....
I'm going to have to
inject you first.
Uh...
바늘 진짜 크다
Oh, that's a big needle.
준비 됐어? / 응
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Yeah...
이건 바이러스를 변형한걸
완화시킨 물질이야
Okay, that was
a modified
version of the viral strain.
이제 네 몸에서 독을
신진대사하면
Now your body metabolizes
the poison
항 바이러스성 혈청이
네 피에서 생성될거야
and the antiviral
serum is going
to be created from
your blood.
독? 독이라고?
Poison? Poison?!
해독제를 주는건지 알았는데?
I thought I was getting
the antidote?
독을 준거란 말이야?
You just gave me poison?!
응. 그게 해독제를
만들 수 있는 유일한 방법이잖아
Yeah.
It's the only way to
make the antidote.
알고 있는거 아니였어?
Did you not
understand that?
오 그거?
Oh, that.
몰랐지. 전체적인
계획만 알았어
Of-- No, I understand
that whole part.
그래 지금 상황이 급박하니까
We're living on the edge.
서두르는게 좋지
Love the rush.
이런 젠장
Oh, damn.
CIA라고?
CIA?
안돼 안돼 뭐야
네가 여길 왜 들어와?
Oh, no, no, no, no,
what are you doing in here?
얘기가 길어요
아무튼 요점은
It's a long story,
but the headline is
사람들을 살리려면
내가 꼭 필요하단거예요
I'm our only hope for survival.
더이상 상황이
나빠지지 않을 줄 알았는데
And here I thought
things couldn't get any worse.
자, 서류가방 안에 보면
중간 크기의 주사기가 있을거야
Okay, inside the briefcase,
is a medisyringe,
multi-dose injector.
네 피를 60cc 뽑아서
I need you to extract 60 cc's
of your own blood,
원심분리기에 넣은 다음에
사람들한테 1cc씩 주사하면돼
put it through the centrifuge,
and then inject
one cc of the antiviral serum
into each of those infected.
응 알았어
Okay, okay.
케이시 여기 ..
아니 아니요 그게 아니고
Casey, here-- No, no,
no, no, no, no.
케이시, 여기, 주사기 들어요
Casey, you have, you
have to take the gun.
주사기 들고
내, 내 피를 뽑아요, 알겠죠?
Take the gun.
And you have to--
You have to take
my blood, okay?
내 피를 뽑아요
So just take my blood.
알았어
Okay.
주사기 들어, 척
Take the gun, Chuck.
네? / 주사기 좀 들어
- Huh?
- Take the gun, Chuck.
뭐라구요? / 주사기 들라고
- What?
- Take the gun.
주사기....
Take the...
이런
Oh, God.
척, 왜 그래?
Chuck, what's happening?
도, 도와줘
케이시는 정신을 잃고 있고
I need-- I need help
right now.
Casey's fading fast!
주사기는 떨어뜨려서
깨져버렸어
The just gun dropped!
And it shattered!
주사기는 그게 다야!
That was the only syringe!
알았으니까 진정해
Okay, uh, stay calm.
다른게 있나 볼게
I'm-I'm going
to find another.
질, 서둘러줘
Jill, please hurry.
시간이 없어
We're running out of time.
시간이 없네요 여러분
Oh, time's running out,
gentlemen.
이제 1분 남았어요
You have one minute left.
하임리히 부분을 못 풀고 있군요
Oh! And I see
you have yet
to attempt the Heimlich
section.
흥미로워요
Interesting.
세상에나!
Oh, good Lord!
제프가 숨이 막힌가봐요!
I think Jeff
is choking!
빨리 누가 하임리힌가
뭔가 좀 해주세요!
Someone should do
the-the Heimlich
or something!
제프, 제프
말할 수 있겠어요?
Jeff, Jeff,
can you speak?
숨이 안 쉬어져요?
Are you choking?
자 일어서요
어서!
Okay, on your feet.
On your feet!
좋아요 내가 셋을 센 후에
All right, on the
count of three
벨트에서 2인치
윗쪽 부분을
I'm going to do an inward
and upward thrust.
안쪽으로, 윗쪽으로 밀칠거예요
Two inches above your
bellbutton.
하나, 둘, 셋!
One, two, three!
주먹을 쥐고 밀쳐올리는걸 반복하고요
??? Repeat four times.
그래 그렇지!
Oh, yes!
다 풀었어요
Done!
어떻게 하죠, 케이시?
What are we gonna
do, Casey?
생각해내봐
Think of something.
너 똑똑하잖아
You're smart.
스탠포드도 다녔다며
You went to Stanford.
중간에 짤렸지만
Sort of.
아 제발
Ugh, God!
입 좀 가려요
Cover your mouth.
속이 다 울렁거리네
That's disgusting!
그래 그거야!
That's it!
미친 소리처럼 들리겠지만,
바이러스는 공기 중으로 퍼지죠?
Hey, hey, this is gonna
sound crazy, but-but
viruses are spread
airborne, right?
응 / 다른 사람들이 재채기하고
- Yeah.
- I mean, you catch them
기침해서 옮은거잖아요 / 응
- when someone sneezes. Coughs.
- Yeah.
그럼 침에서도 항 바이러스 물질이
신진대사를 하겠죠?
Well, maybe the antivirals
metabolize in saliva.
무슨 소릴 하는거야?
What a you talking about?
내가 이런 짓을 해야 한다니
I can't believe
I'm about to do this.
뭐?
What?
안돼 싫어!
No, no!
안돼. 절대 안돼
No, no, no, no.
난 내 나라를 위해서
명예롭게 일해왔어
I served my country with
honor, Bartowski.
제발
Please.
적어도 명예는 지키면서
죽게 해줘
Let me die with
my dignity.
척?
Chuck?
질! / 뭐하는거야?
- Jill!
- What are you doing?
질, 질, 그게
Jill, Jill, hey.
항 바이러스성 물질이 침을
통해서도 퍼질 수 있지 않을까 해서
I thought that-- I thought
that maybe the antivirals
could be spread
by saliva.
말도 안 되는 소리야
That's ridiculous.
생화학에서 낙제한 이유가 있네
No wonder
you failed biochem.
진심으로, 정말 정말 미안해요
From the deepest
recesses
of my soul, I'm sorry.
또 올 게 왔구나
Oh, here we go again.
넌 절반을 맡아
Okay, you take
half the room,
난 나머지 절반을 맡을게
사람당 1cc야
I'll take the other.
One cc each.
자 어서 서둘러
Okay? Hurry.
자 놓을게요 케이시
Okay, okay. Casey, Casey.
Ah.
수고하셨어요
카마이클 요원님!
Way to go,
Agent Carmichael!
척!
Chuck!
정말 대단했어
You're amazing.
아니야
Nah.
그래 뭐 조금은
Well, maybe a little.
이제 질 로버츠가 척이
요원이라는 사실을 아는데
Jill Roberts
now knows Chuck's an asset.
장군님께선 어떻게 하길 원하십니까?
What do you want us
to do about it?
아무것도 하지 말게
I want you to do nothing.
워커 요원이 죽인 암살범은
풀크럼 요원으로 밝혀졌네
The assassin Agent Walker shot
was a member of Fulcrum.
변절한 CIA 요원이었어
A rogue CIA agent.
현재 그 쪽에서
얼마나 침투했는지 몰라
We don't know the extent
of their penetration.
풀크럼에서 질에게
접촉해올 가능성이 있어
If Jill knows something
they may make a play for her.
그럼 질을 미끼로
쓰자는 말씀이십니까?
So, you want to use her as bait?
장군님. 척이 질을 좋아해요
General, uh, Chuck has real
feelings for Jill.
척이 우리가 질을 미끼로 쓰는걸
찬성할 것 같지 않은데요
I don't think he'd approve of us
using her like this.
그러니 척에게 말하지 말라는거네
워커 요원
That's why you're not going
to tell him, Agent Walker.
Wow.
오랜만에 보는데
That's something I haven't seen
in a while.
뭐가, 이 옷?
What, this--
일주일에 4번이나 입는데
I wear this like
four times a week.
아니 네 웃음 말이야
No, your smile.
행복해보여
You look happy.
응
Yeah.
응 그거
Yeah, that.
그거 말이구나
That thing.
글쎄
Um, I don't know.
아마..
I guess, uh,
내가 궁금해하던 문제들의
답을 찾아내서 그런가봐
I found some of
those answers
that you said I was
looking for.
아 고마워라
Well, thank God.
이제야 안심이 돼
I am so relieved.
난 있지, 항상 새라한테
뭔가 특별한게 있다고 생각했어
I just think that,
you know, Sarah--
There's really something
special about her.
네가 질하고 있었던
여러 일을 거치면서
I think that you had
to go through all that stuff
드디어 새라가
네 천생연분이란걸 깨달았나봐
with Jill so you could figure
out who the one is for you.
이제 깨달았으니까
더이상 다른 사람엔 신경쓰지마
And now that
you found her
you'll stop
wondering
about somebody else.
받아
Take it.
새라한테 내 안부 전해줘
Tell Sarah I said hi.
나야
Hey.
내가 제일 좋아하는 비밀 요원님
잘 계세요?
How's my favorite secret agent?
응
Um... good.
응, 잘 있지
Yeah, good.
바이모어에서
CPR 시험봐서 공부할거야
I just-- I have to study
for a CPR test for my day job
at the Buy More.
네가 인공호흡 공부하는거
도와주면 되겠다
I could use some help
with the mouth-to-mouth.
네 가짜 여자친구는 어떻게 해?
Well, what about your cover
girlfriend?
질투하지 않을까?
Won't she be jealous?
아니야
No.
우리 사이는 그냥 위장 커플이라
No, our-our relationship's
a cover, you know.
질투하고 그런거 없어
There's nothing
to be jealous about.
그 모든게...
So everything...
가짜라는거지
it's all fake.
정말 외롭겠다, 척
That sounds really lonely,
Chuck.
응 외로워
Yeah, it is.
하지만...
But...
이젠 네가 있으니깐
진실된걸 할 수 있겠지
but now that you're here maybe
we can have something real.
우리 둘이서
Us. Together.
그 얘기 듣기 좋다
I like the sound of that.
그래, 그 인공호흡 말인데...
So about that mouth-to-mouth...
자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)